[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Back in the day...
I used to play basketball all the time,
but once I started working, there was...
There was hardly any time left.
Do I still have the moves?
Yes, you do.
Give me a hand here.
I'm going to take my pants off.
I'll turn the water on for you.
Wait.
See?
I can't even stand up.
Help me get into the tub.
Also, could you grab me a bathrobe?
What are you so shy about?
We have the same parts.
Could you pull me up?
Did you know...
building a body like this...
takes more than just working out?
I didn't.
The most important part is...
right here.
Do you know how important the waist is?
You'll understand once you're older.
Have you ever slept with anyone?
The noodles are ready.
I'll go get them.
Whoa.
This looks good.
I didn't know you were such a good cook.
I'm only doing this because I hurt your leg.
-Want to have some? -No, thanks.
Oh, leaving already?
I have plans to have dinner with Itt.
Hey, don't tell him I sprained my ankle,
or he'll rush over here, okay?
Yeah.
Hey.
Isn't that a bit too formal?
First impressions are everything.
You're dressed way too casually.
You're going to get an earful from my brother.
Isn't this normal?
Why?
Worried I won't be around to help you?
You promised you'd help me.
Yeah, I will. Let's go.
Mr. Ing,
the document you just signed was...
a request to increase the budget
by over 20 million.
So?
Look, Secretary Piang.
Don't be such a stress-head.
Try to enjoy life, would you?
Just look at me.
Right now, I'm...
enjoying the taste of victory before it's mine
because the key to Pattaya...
is about to walk right through that door.
Oh, Mr. Yok...
Exactly.
Understood.
In that case,
I'll arrange a desk for Mr. Yok
as close to your office as possible.
I'll also set the AC to the perfect temperature
and give him the best view.
If anyone so much as lays a finger
on him,
the fire alarm will go off immediately.
Secretary Piang,
could you check
if there are any site visits
on our schedule?
Do you want to see the site,
or do you want to see Mr. Yok?
The site, obviously. Why would I want to see Yok?
You know, in just...
three, two, one...
What the fuck?
That outfit is a total fashion disaster.
What do you think this place is?
A playground?
If you're here for a stroll, do it outside.
I think talent should matter more than an outfit.
Secretary Piang,
that's Gen Z for you.
I like it. It shows character.
If you have any questions,
ask Piang.
Which department should I put them in?
Which department do you want to intern at?
-I'm fine with anything. -Really?
Secretary Piang,
have Auntie Chai...
transferred to another position,
and put Itt in as the housekeeper instead.
Fifteen thousand a month, alright?
P'Ing,
I was just kidding.
This is a professional office.
What are you supposed to call me?
Mr. Ing...
Secretary Piang,
put Itt
in Corporate Development.
He'll be right at the front lines
so he can finally get some serious work experience.
-Mr. Ing... -As for Yok, stay here in this office.
You'll be my personal assistant.
I know exactly what Itt is capable of.
And Yok, you are...
a minor in finance
with top-tier grades.
No wonder
you seem so composed.
Having you assist me is for the best.
Secretary Piang is swamped.
You can help her out as well.
Understood.
Good.
Time for some grooming.
What do you mean?
Having a distinct character is fine,
but from now on,
you represent me.
Come on, let's give you a makeover.
I can go buy new clothes
with Itt after work.
That won't do.
My time is too valuable.
I can't wait until you're off the clock.
What?
Do you need a formal letter from the CEO or something?
Follow me.
Mr. Itt, please follow me
to the Corporate Development department.
It's the department where...
Hey, Pete.
Hi.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
You finally reached out to me.
I thought you'd forgotten about your old flame.
And...
who's this?
This is Yok,
my new assistant.
Oh, my God.
He's stunning.
His face is a masterpiece.
Can I touch him?
I'm just going to take some measurements.
Measure him carefully.
Find a style that I'll actually like.
Of course.
As for you...
-Hurry it up. -Based on, uh...
You can try something on.
Right this way, please.
So handsome.
Stunning.
Are you ready for the first look?
Uh-huh.
Ta-da.
Okay.
Next one.
So gorgeous.
Wow, so handsome.
This one's good. Next.
The third look...
Next.
Are you tired?
Ta-da.
This is the final look, Ing.
Is that it?
I actually wanted him to try on ten outfits.
Never mind. I'll take them all.
I'll be waiting outside.
Yes.
Here you go.
Everything's ready.
Thanks a lot.
-See you later. -Yeah.
See ya.
What? Are you not coming?
Do you have a thing for the guy with pink hair?
Today was exhausting.
You're off the clock. Why are you still here?
How much did everything cost?
What?
All these clothes.
Oh...
I don't know.
I'll check the total with P'Piang tomorrow
and pay you back right away.
Don't worry about it.
I bought them for you.
Don't worry about the money.
Mr. Ing,
how could I let you buy all of this for me?
Well...
I bought these as a gift for you
so you'll feel more motivated.
Sound good?
Thank you, Mr. Ing.
But I'd rather just accept
your kindness.
You truly are Minister Pongpaisan's son.
Showing respect to both others and yourself.
Okay,
you win.
I'll put it on my card for now.
You can pay me back once you get your salary, okay?
Okay.
Money isn't the hard part,
but the work...
is where the real challenge starts.
I'm always ready.
Excuse me.
What's stressing you out?
I need to find a good piece of land
at a good price.
Any ideas where?
How about Rayong? It's a major economic hub.
Or Chiang Rai? It connects to both Laos and China.
You're right. Thanks a lot, man.
Stop thinking like that. It's just stupid.
So you'll have the strength to keep pushing on.
Hello? I'll send it right away.
Sure.
Yok, keep up, or you'll fall behind.
Up here, right?
Yes, put it down here instead.
Yok, take notes.
And over there...
I'll go with this plan.
Let's work together to make this project...
Dinner is on me.
You know the rule, no one's going home sober.
You bet.
Eat up.
You've gotten so thin from working so hard.
Take this, P'Phet.
Aren't you eating?
I'm fine.
To be honest, I'm really glad
I got to meet you today, Mr. Phet.
Me, too. My brother mentions you quite often.
Yes, Mr. Ing?
Secretary Piang,
have Yok come see me immediately.
Understood.
Go. Don't waste time,
or he'll blow a fuse again.
He doesn't want me anymore, I see.
Mr. Ing, it's payday.
I've already paid for the clothes.
Forget about that.
You're coming with me to Damnoen Saduak.
What are we going there for?
I'll tell you on the way.
The proposals submitted to the government official
suddenly ran into problems.
All the documents
have been sent back for revisions.
The budget, the team,
or the entire plan...
We're waiting on a single document.
I can't afford to mess this up.
Getting a minister and investors together
is no easy feat.
We need to make this deal happen.
Uncle Jeng, please turn the AC up.
I'm freezing here.
Understood.
Do you have a cold?
Should we stop and get some medicine?
To nip it in the bud, you know.
No need.
It's nothing serious. I'll be fine after a quick nap.
By the way, is that data ready?
Let me have a look.
I'm screwed.
Yok, can you hold your liquor?
Why do you ask?
It's these investors.
They drink like fish
as if there's no tomorrow.
They won't let us leave until we're wasted.
Aren't you a heavy drinker yourself?
Look at me now.
After two glasses, I'll be down for the count.
Anyway, book a hotel for me today.
Sure.
Make sure it's near the place.
Hopefully, I'll be able to crawl back.
Today is extremely important.
Whether you drink or not,
you have to keep me in check.
We need to close this deal at any cost.
If we can do that,
we'll have the chance
to move on to the Pattaya project.
And if we pull it off,
you'll have something to show off to your brother.
This is just how business is.
Having a successful father has its perks,
but once you actually start working,
people act all nice to your face,
but behind your back? Jeez...
It's a different story.
They just go through the motions.
I went through the same thing
when I started out in my 20s.
I thought people would respect me.
Not a single one did.
I faced all kinds of problems.
Damn it.
It's always just me.
It's cold as hell.
Get some sleep.
I'll wake you up when we get there.
I never would have guessed...
that you're so good at taking care of people.
Wake me up when we arrive.
It's such an honor, Minister.
-Please enjoy yourselves. -We will.
Here's to destiny.
Thank you, Minister Tawan
and Mr. Ing,
for honoring us with your presence today.
-Cheers. -Cheers.
This second glass is to sincerity.
Whether our partnership succeeds...
depends on how sincere we are with each other.
Don't you agree, Mr. Ing?
Have some more.
Excellent.
The third glass...
I can't get out of this one, can I?
Let this glass be...
a testament to my sincerity to everyone.
-Come on. -Let's go, bottoms up.
If you want to do business with me, you need to be bold.
Finish this, and I'll sign the contract right away.
-Drink up. Drink up. -Drink up. Drink up.
Please.
Bottoms up.
Empty it all.
-Go for it. -Do it.
-Drink. -Drink up.
-Whoa. -Whoa.
Mr. Jomthup,
I'd like to take this drink on behalf of Mr. Ing.
Yok...
You might not understand how we do things here.
Exactly.
My father was just talking
about you the other day, Mr. Jomthup.
He enjoyed talking with you about the northern project.
Mr. Ravit,
my brother speaks very highly of your vision.
Well then, let's go.
Drink up.
So, I'd like to raise this glass
as a toast to my respect for all of you.
It's our pleasure.
-Bottoms up. -Drink.
Drink.
Not bad at all.
Have another round.
-Keep them coming. -Another one.
There's still some left. Keep it going.
Don't stop.
P'Ing, stay still.
Wait.
Normally...
aren't you someone
who can separate work from personal life?
Taking care of my boss is part of my job.
Your boss never taught you anything like this.
I'm leaving, then.
Hold on.
Come here.
Come over here.
Look...
Just a second.
I feel better now.
Much better.
You're quite good at taking care of people.
Thanks a lot. I feel a lot better now.
Go wash your shirt. It's filthy.
Get out of the car.
We drove all this way...
just to look at a wasteland?
This isn't just any ordinary wasteland.
It's the fruit of our success from yesterday.
Come to think of it...
you can really hold your liquor, can't you?
I never would've pegged you for that type.
To be honest, if I weren't sick,
I would've outdrunk those old geezers.
So, are you recovered now?
Of course.
I'm fit as a fiddle.
If you don't believe me...
want to find out?
You're never going to stop, are you?
Jeez, why so serious?
Alright.
We're here.
From now on, this area...
will be where your first building stands.
My first building?
Yes.
This will be...
the first building you'll oversee for this project.
What's with the confused look?
No need to get sentimental.
You've earned it, Yok.
Aren't you going to set foot
on the site you'll be managing?
From now on,
this area is your responsibility.
Alright, we should get moving.
There's someone important I want to introduce.
Why are you just standing there?
Hurry up.
Where are we?
You little rascal.
Finally decided to visit your grandpa, huh?
Grandpa, that was a pretty hard pat on the back.
Judging by that strength, you'll probably...
live to be at least a hundred and twenty.
Why would I want to live that long?
Tell me if you're lonely.
I'll find you a wife.
Are you serious?
Come on, let's head inside.
Oh?
Whose kid is this?
This is Minister Pongpaisan's son.
He's interning with me,
so I brought him along to meet you.
I see, so it's Pong's grandson.
You certainly have a keen eye for people.
Hello, Grandpa. I'm Yok.
My, look how much you've grown.
When you were just a little thing,
I used to carry you around.
Not that you'd remember.
Your grandfather was a stubborn man.
He was dead set on giving you a girl's name.
He said Yok, or jade, is as precious as diamonds.
Everyone tried to stop him, of course,
but no one could change his mind.
It's a good thing they couldn't.
I think this piece of jade is...
quite precious indeed.
Why are we standing here baking in the sun?
Let's go inside.
-It's boiling out here. Follow me. -Alright.
Know what tree this is?
This is called a Pong-pong tree.
Don't ever eat those fruits.
They're lethal.
And this one...
When I was a kid, Grandpa tricked me.
He told me it was a banana tree.
I waited for it to bear fruit,
but in the end, it didn't.
This one...
is a Ti plant.
Pretty, isn't it?
Not as pretty as me, I guess.
Look at this.
I got some pond snails yesterday.
I'm going to make a red curry for you.
You two, go catch some fish.
I want two big...
nice ones.
Putting us to work again?
Yong has the fishing rods ready for you.
Same old rule.
If the fish don't weigh at least two kilograms,
you have to do the dishes tonight.
Okay.
Just like always, right?
Did you hear that?
If you don't want your hands getting all pruney...
show me what you've got.
Grandpa, he's just putting on an act.
He usually knows how to smile.
He just smiles.
You got it, Grandpa.
Oh, so you can talk.
You brought me all this way just to fish?
Yok,
let me ask you something.
How were you raised?
Why do you have to
question everything before doing anything?
We're humans. Just do whatever you want.
Want to swim? Swim. Want to fish? Fish.
Eat whatever you want.
Why overthink everything?
Come on.
Why are you just standing there?
Hurry and bring me some water.
Hurry up.
Why aren't you coming?
Scared of me?
Aw, you're scaring me now.
What?
How do you like that?
Having fun, huh?
P'Ing...
P'Ing.
P'Ing, aren't we fishing anymore?
Come on, forget about the fish.
Let's just swim for now.
You little rascal.
I told you to fish, but all you did was swim.
You've been like this since you were a kid.
You haven't changed either, Grandpa.
Still nagging me after all these years.
Thailand is just so hot, you know?
Didn't I catch the fish
you wanted, anyway?
We got about three or four kilos, right?
Yes.
You're quite something, aren't you?
Hey, where are you going?
I've got the good stuff.
He means the liquor.
Have some.
Yong, bring the glasses over here.
This is Karanda fruit.
I grew it and pickled it with my own two hands.
Now...
Give me the glasses.
Who do you think I take after?
Here.
-Make sure you look after your health, too. -Alright.
Three shots.
Wait, Grandpa. I'll drink with you.
Yok doesn't drink.
That's a very unique flavor.
I thought you said he didn't drink.
Look who's got egg on his face.
Look at you, you little puppy...
Traveling all this way,
don't tell me...
that you only came here just to visit me.
What kind of trouble are you cooking up this time?
Come on, you're accusing me already?
Are you really my grandpa or what?
Of course I am.
Why else would I bother worrying about you?
So, what are you really doing here?
Okay, you win.
It's just about the hotel project.
The connections hit a snag,
so things are getting delayed.
I've already sunk all my money into it.
Eventually,
I'll have to find a new way forward.
You don't need to worry at all.
Looking for a way out is one thing,
but don't break the rules.
I know.
Don't think having a reputation
means you'll get a free pass.
Focus on your work
and keep yourself on the right track.
Do you hear me?
Understood.
I hear you.
Ing here is quite hot-tempered.
Don't let him lead you astray.
What, Grandpa?
How could someone like me lead him astray?
P'Ing has been taking very good care of me.
Well said.
Then let's have dinner.
Come on.
Yok, keep telling me more
about your grandfather.
Of course.
Have some curry with pond snails.
I made it myself.
Honestly,
I feel for you.
Here we go again.
When you were a kid,
what you went through...
was more than anyone could take.
If your mother were still around...
That's enough, Grandpa.
That was a long time ago,
and it's all in the past now.
You don't have to worry.
I'm not gonna jump off a building over this.
That's just how old people are. We talk and talk.
Anyway, you two...
must be exhausted by now.
I'm getting sleepy.
Not at all.
-What? -I've enjoyed talking with you, Grandpa.
This one is quite the smooth talker.
If only Ing were half as smooth-talking as you are,
I'd be much more at ease.
Not at all.
I've enjoyed talking with you, Grandpa.
You really are something...
Hey, Yong.
That's enough, Grandpa.
-Go... -Grandpa.
I'll have him get the guest room ready for Yok.
Yok and I can just share my room.
Right? We don't mind a bit of a squeeze.
Right, the silent treatment.
I'll take that as a yes.
Thanks for having me.
Take good care of Yok, alright?
I will.
Sorry about this.
My grandpa is all about that low-carbon lifestyle,
so there's no AC. Just this old-school fan.
You can handle it, right?
It's fine. It's not that hot anyway.
I'm going to hit the shower.
Don't you dare peek.
It's your turn now.
Yok...
Yok,
wake up.
Go take a shower.
No...
You have to.
How can you go to bed without showering first?
Go shower.
Go take a shower.
Go.
Your towel is over here.
He ruined everything.
Oh...
I spilled some water all over the blanket.
We'll have to share this one.
Hurry up and turn off the lights.
Get to bed.
Hey.
Aren't you hot in long sleeves?
I'm not.
You'll be too hot to sleep in a bit. Come here.
-Let me help you take them off. -I'm fine.
What? I was just trying to tuck you in.
Suit yourself.
If you don't want the blanket, fine.
Don't come crying to me if you get sick.
Earlier today,
you didn't seem to care if I got sick.
Why are you holding such a grudge?
Sorry, I'm a side sleeper.
-What are you doing? -I'm just trying to cover you up.
Wait, where are you going?
I'm just trying to tuck you in.
It's nothing.
Come here. I told you to cover up.
That hurts.
Wait, where are you going?
Come visit again when you're free.
Grandpa, I'm not leaving soon.
Who was talking to you?
Grandpa...
Just who is your actual grandson here?
Hey.
Want to try dating each other?
Whether I like women or not,
there's no way we could be together.
I've endured this for long enough.